

DETAILS

- winnaingsoe6666@gmail.com
- +66960308914 (WhatsApp)
- winnaingsoe.mm (Line)
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ win-naing-soe
- (iii) 07 Aug 1996
- ⚠ Chiang Mai, Thailand, 50230
- Notice period permitting (1 months)

☐ HARD SKILLS

- Java, Java swing
- Spring MVC, Spring Boot
- PostgreSQL, MySQL, Stored procedure
- Angular, JavaScript, JSP, jQuery
- GitHub, SVN, Jira, Jenkins, GitLab CI/CD
- Shell Scripting, Excel VBA
- Cypress, Selenium
- Maven, Apache Ant, Apache Tomcat, JBoss, Node.js
- Familiar with AWS
- Linux

Mr. WIN NAING SOE

Software Engineer

Software Engineer with over 4 years of experience in designing and developing Windows and Web applications from initial to final deliverable. Passionate about learning new technologies and happy to make things happen for users with strong ability to analyze complex projects and make clean requirements for other team members.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

04/2023 – present Myanmar

DIR-ACE Technology, Offshore development Team Duties and Responsibilities:

- Collaborated with clients on design outlines, creating detailed documentation after incorporating their feedback.
- Developed and maintained secure, scalable web applications (Java, Spring Boot), desktop applications (Java Swing), automation tools (shell scripts), and stored procedures.
- Implemented advanced security measures and reduce vulnerabilities by 65%.
- Conducted unit testing, integration testing, and performance testing.
- Created comprehensive technical documentation for clear understanding and easy maintenance.
- Created detailed RD explanation sections for clear project understanding by team members.
- Monitored project progress and resource utilization, maximizing efficiency.
- Improved code quality through code reviews and mentored junior developers, ensuring their continuous professional growth.
- Developed and implemented software solutions
 - Web App Development with JAVA and Spring boot
 - Desktop App Development with Java Swing
 - API Developments
 - Web App Developments with Angular
 - Stored Procedure developments
 - Shell Script Developments
 - Automation Tools development with Excel micro-VBA
- Tools: Java, Java Swing, Spring boot, SQL, PostgreSQL, Stored procedure, Angular, JavaScript, Linux, Jira, Git, CI/CD Shell Script, Excel VBA
- **Achievements:** Awarded the President's Award for Good Progress in Productivity and Quality Assurance (Quality Assurance Award).

Software Engineer

4/2022 - 3/2023

Myanmar

DIR-ACE Technology, Offshore development Team Duties and Responsibilities:

- Contributed to REST API development using Java for improved system capabilities.
- Refactored complex stored procedures for SIMM calculations, enhancing code readability and optimizing performance for faster initial margin (IM) calculations.
- Troubleshooted and resolved JBoss server configuration issues for optimal performance.
- Built a reporting system for KPIs, cost & schedule management for all offshore projects, and interactive dashboards using Angular.
- Adapted PostgreSQL Stored Procedures for use with SQL Server, ensuring database compatibility across platforms.
- Tools: Java, Spring boot, Angular, PostgreSQL, Stored procedure, JBoss, Jira, Git

■ EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (Electronics) Technological University, Kalay, 2012-2018

Certified ITPEC

Fundamental Information Technology Engineers Examination (FE), 2023

≜SOFT SKILLS

- Strong analytical and problem solving skills
- ❖ Exceptional teamwork and collaboration abilities
- *Responsibility & Flexible attitude
- Hardworking
- **❖** Fast learning

■ LANGUAGE

Burmese

Native

English

Intermediate

Japanese

Basic

▲INTERESTS

- Football
- Travelling
- Music
- Reading

Full Stack Developer

11/2020 - 05/2023

DIR-ACE Technology, Myanmar Association of Japan Alumni (MAJA)

JLPT Registration System Project

- Developed a multi-tiered web application for online submission of Japanese Language Proficiency Test (JLPT) forms.
- Implemented user interfaces and backend services for applicants, operators, and administrators.
- Integrated payment gateway (2C2P) for handling online transactions.
- Managed form applies, test site setup, test term management, and reporting functionalities.
- Ensured the application's performance, security, and reliability by conducting endto-end testing, unit testing, integration testing, performance testing, and load
- Designed the system to handle high concurrency, supporting thousands of simultaneous user transactions and ensuring smooth performance during peak usage times.
- Created comprehensive technical documentations, Software Requirements Specification (SRS) and deployment guides.
- Tools: Rocky Linux, Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Security, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, ¡Query, HTML/CSS, Cypress, Git, CI/CD, 2C2P
- **Achievements:**
 - Successfully launched the application, facilitating thousands of applicants to register and manage their JLPT exams online.
 - Streamlined administrative tasks and improved reporting accuracy for the client, Myanmar Association of Japan Alumni (MAJA).
 - Awarded the President's Award for Best System Development Award
 - https://www.ilpt-maja.org.mm/?language=en

Junior Programmer

03/2020 - 04/2022

DIR-ACE Technology, Offshore development Team

Myanmar

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Streamlined daily trade processing by developing a new function and user interface for pre-trade calculations.
- Developed automation programs using Shell Script and VBA tools to streamline workflows.
- Automated comprehensive testing of the stock price derivative calculation system using Selenium.
- Independently identified problems, analyzed impact areas, and reporting survey documents.
- Developed common Stored Procedures with a shell script for efficient database interactions.
- Utilized Oracle SQL for code refactoring and database performance optimization.
- Tools: Java 8, Java Swing, Spring boot, JSP, Shell Script, SQL, Git, REST API

Junior Programmer (Internship)

12/2019 - 03/2020

DIR-ACE Technology, Internship, Talent program

Myanmar

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Developed Attendance Management System
- Collaborated with senior developers to design and implement a comprehensive attendance management system.
- Created an ER diagram and designed a relational database using MySQL for efficient data storage and retrieval.
- Implemented user interface (UI) functionalities using JSP, HTML, CSS, ¡Query, and Bootstrap for a user-friendly experience.
- Developed user registration, role management, and reporting features to ensure secure access and data visualization.
- Utilized version control (SVN) for code management and collaboration.
- Tools: Java 8, Spring MVC, MyBatis, JSP, Jasper reports, MySQL, SVN, HTML, CSS, ¡Query, and Bootstrap